Thank you for watching!
Nogizaka Oseibo Grand Prix
The most junior member, Gokisei, will choose one of her favorite senpai who has been a great help to her and express her gratitude to them with her Oseibo.
and express their gratitude with Oseibo.
Senpai will run if they think they can get one and if they don't, they will get one.
If they don't, they will be punished with a drink in the worst case.
the worst punishment is a drink!
Tonight, let's see who from the past has been a big help to us
Now, senior members who say, "I, too, will be taken care of by IYOKI!
Raise your hand!
Come on, come on!
Well, we're here, we're here, we're here, we're here!
Here are the five who ran for the position of "IYOKI and Soshiai".
Mr. Yamashita, I have an image that you don't come out for this kind of project very often.
I have an image that you don't come out for this kind of projects.
Yes, sir.
Well, he failed miserably when he was a member of Yomiki Seimei.
Well, let's hear it.
We're the same people who caught the Tachio fish.
I see.
On location together.
We were on the first location together.
And for my birthday this year, he gave me a bed of nuka-doko as a present.
Delicious bed of rice bran.
I can't believe he went to the trouble of buying such a heavy bed of rice bran for me.
This must be love.
I'm sure
I don't think I could do it.
I think it's already decided. I think you've already decided.
That's not good.
Next, Kawaki.
In a row!
Consecutive hits!
Thank you very much.
I don't go out to eat with members very often.
Yes, yes, yes.
But you are the only one I went out to eat with.
That's an encounter, isn't it?
What did you eat?
Yakiniku.
Oh!
That's right.
But it wasn't from me, it was from you.
from Eiyoki
I have some time before the next
I have some time before the next site, so he asked me if I'd like to go.
Wow!
It's already decided, isn't it?
Dinner is a great way to close the gap between you and me.
It brings us closer.
You're a serial killer, aren't you, Kaki?
I'm sure you'd like to take pictures.
I'm sure he'll do it again next time.
You're a serial shooter, aren't you?
Yes.
I was wondering what you'd want me to do.
I've been with you on shaved ice. I've been on shaved ice with you too.
Shaved ice
Yes, shaved ice. I love shaved ice.
I like shaved ice a lot.
Iyoki invited me.
What?
That's a lot of invitations from you.
Don't ask me out!
Also, she had a camera and took a lot of pictures with it.
I thought she likes me.
He took a lot of pictures.
It's like yakiniku versus shaved ice.
Yes, it is.
Yes, Seimiya.
When I first came here, I said in an interview that I liked Seimiya.
I said in an interview that I liked you.
I said that.
This pattern is pretty strong.
It's very strong.
I was so happy to hear that for the first time that I gave her a cup of my favorite tea and she gave it back to me.
I see.
But Mr. Himura is terrible.
Oh, my.
This is where they say you've had a lot of interaction with the goki.
That's nice.
Why did you think you'd get the Black Sea?
You know...
My childhood friend from Hong Kong was a friend of your mother's.
Oh?Oh, my.
Oh, seriously.
That's...
Coincidence.
There's a familial connection.
There's a connection.
First of all
I was with Iyoki until just before the local show during the national tour, and we joked around in front of each other at the tour launch and so on.
I see.
I guess being on tour must have been a big part of it.
Yes, it was.
We also took care of each other.
There's also the relationship between the families.
Well, that's the basis of being a caretaker, isn't it?
That's part of it.
That's right.
I wonder who is the senior whom Iyoki wants to give the caretaker boy to?
Hmmm...
Yeah...
Aaah!
He's not here.
He's not there.
He's a good seater. - He's a good seater.
He's a good fitter.
I see... there's a pattern here.
Is this hard even for Ioki?
And who did Ioki want to give it to?
Sakura-san!
It was Endo.
It's Endo. Endo.
Why didn't it come out?
I was so good at pretending I was alive.
During the tour, I got a little depressed.
I was crying at the end of the stage.
He didn't ask me what happened.
He was there for about 30 minutes without asking me what happened.
That's what happened.
I was very grateful and happy about that.
I see.
There was an episode of that too.
But from Endo's point of view, it wasn't anything special.
No, but...
What is it? What is it?
Yes. Like that.
Thank you very much.
And Ioki presents Endo with a bouquet of cherry blossoms.
Well, isn't it wonderful that they have a relationship like that?
And it's not over.
This isn't the end.
Punishment drink after such a good time?
Go ahead, drink up.
We're holding hands.
I'm holding your hand.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but thank you for making this happen so quickly.
Next, Ichinose confesses his feelings for his senpai.
I'm sure Ichinose will give it to you.
Please raise your hand.Raise your hands, please.
Last three, three, three.
Here are the three who have run for the office!
You're smiling, Iwamoto.
What's wrong?
This year's tour...
Why are you laughing?
It's just really funny.
But he always tells me he really likes me.
Mi-kun is very charming and the older members love him a lot.
I'm not too sure, but I'm not the type to go out of my way to make a move on a younger guy.
But he's so cute that I can't look at his face.
I like him so much that I react a little weird.
I mean, I like myself.
So that's what I mean.
Uh-huh.
Yes, I see.
Mr. Yamashita.
A series of shots?
A string of them.
I have conclusive evidence.
What's that?
We went out for dinner the other night.
We went out to eat.
We did.
We rode in the car together.
She said she was too nervous to go with Minuki.
If he likes someone more than me, I'd have to die.
I can't breathe.
So I'm sure it's me. So I'm pretty sure it's me now.
You've been going out to dinner with him?
What did you go out to eat?
Yakiniku.
Why are you asking me what I ate?
I think it's important.
Among men and women... you used to say you went to yakiniku.
Yakiniku.
Tamora.
When I was on the national tour this year, when Mi-kyun was doing MC.
I was doing a little joke when Miyuki was doing the MC.
When we were rehearsing, Mayu-san asked me to watch it.
She showed it to me once, and then she told me what she was going to do.
She would come in front of me at a convenience store and say, "Please watch Mayu-san.
Shoplifting.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm not asking you to look at my guts.
Look at what, at the convenience store?
They put in a few regional one-liners every once in a while.
I have them test it all the time.
If Mahi laughs, it's easier to talk to him.
It's easier to talk to him.
Remember when I said, "Wait a minute, please watch this at the convenience store"?
The jumping joker flash with the dancing tyrannosaurus.
Tyrannosaurus.
You're funny all the time.
Much funnier.Much more interesting.
Come on, seniors, look at this.
Here we go.
Look, it's somewhat funny.
Slightly funny.
It's good.
Is there anyone among them to whom Ichinose would like to give a year-end gift?
Let's go.
Oh, no, no, no!
Oh no... oh no... oh no...
Wow!
Wow.
Dummkopf, you're in shock.
You'll be shocked if he doesn't show up.
When I felt the wind, I thought...
I thought, "Oh, it's coming.
It's coming.
Shame on you, Iwamoto.
Ichinose isn't coming.
You're laughing.
I totally brought my eyebrows to his shoulders.
Dummkopf was so surprised.
"He's not coming!
She's not coming!
He's not coming!
Did you see that face?
Ichinose expresses his love to Yamashita by giving him his favorite cod roe.
What was the decisive reason why you chose Yamashita?
I really loved him for a long time, so having him around makes me want to do my best every day.I really loved it for a long time, so when Mr. Mizuki was around, I could do my best every day.
He also took me out to dinner and took care of me a lot.
If you stay in a small space in a car for the rest of your life, you can't breathe, right?
I'm really shaking with pain.
You know...
That's right.
You're running out of oxygen.
You're going to eat, right?
Yes, that's why.
You're eating? We ate together.
We ate a lot.
How can you eat so much?
Next, four people including Mr. Tamura and Mr. Iwamoto of Renshun ran for the contest.
Mr. Tsutsui
Iwamoto
Yes, sir.
You think Matsukishi will give it to you?
What? Because he likes me so much.
(Laughs)
(laughs)
I really like what Shokichi says.
It's so great, it's true.
I couldn't look at Renca's face for more than 10 seconds... she's so cute.
That's a lie. Come forward for a second.
Let's do 10 seconds.
Here we go.
Ten, nine, eight, seven.Ten. Nine. Eight. Seven.
Cute.
Is that possible?
Why not?
Satsuki loves you among her fans.
She's famous for it.
I see. So it's obvious to everyone watching this.
Is that what you mean?
Maybe it'll be a surprise to the fans if they don't get it.
I see.
That's what I'm talking about.
You didn't go out to dinner?
I didn't go to dinner.
You're not going out to dinner?
Come on, Tamura.
Yes, we went to dinner.
Oh, wow.
You're strong.
The food's strong.
And for good luck, we'll do some cycling together.
There it is!
The legendary cycling that gave him the name Shokichi
The cycling in Chiba
I also heard from a fan
Yes.
Next, you like Mayu-chan, don't you?
Wait a minute.
Then it's just the two of us who are watching.
I think the fans will be surprised if they don't get this.
What?Oh, what?
I was going to give you Iwamoto.
No, you didn't.
We went out for dinner.
We went to dinner.
What did you eat?
You didn't ask me earlier.
Yes, I did.
We went to a barbecue.
Yakiniku?
Wait a minute... why do you only go out for yakiniku?
What's wrong with Nogizaka?
But I'm pretty sure about the yakiniku.
Yakiniku is a definite possibility.
Yakiniku is pretty much the only thing they do before they join the group.
That's right.
That's a big reach.
With these two, it's too close to call.
It's a one-two so far.
Don't worry.
Shibata, what?
It's all right.
What's up with that?
Before every show, he asks me to touch his cheek.
Every time he comes to touch my cheek.
He touches my cheek.
Touching her cheek is a big deal, isn't it?
It's so nice, isn't it?
Lately, he's been very flirtatious with me.
I think he's really opened up to me.I think you've forgiven me quite a bit, and
Sacchan writes on your blog and writes about me...
Yes.
I've seen you send me messages by e-mail.
I think your fans would be a little surprised if you didn't give it to me.
That's what all three of you do for your fans.
You three are strong.
Tsutsui, this is the third time.
Tsutsui, you've been thinning the sauce.
Tsutsumi, are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
Every time I see him, he's cute dozens of times.
He tells me I'm cute.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know what to say when someone says I'm cute.
So I just tsun him right away.
I get tsunted.
Why do you get tsunned when someone says you're cute?
You're so thin.
Compared to the other three, it's a little thin.
How long does it take to get a tsun?
Do it a little bit.
Just a little.
Then say it.
Ehime, you're so cute today!
Thank you very much.
A tsun version.
"Gradually tsun"?
I see... "gradually tsun"...
Ehime-san is so cute, I really love her! Ehime-san is still so cute and I really love her!
Thank you so much!
Ehime-san is super cute!
LOL!
What's with this "I'm going to do it"?
That's because you say it as Ren-chan.
You say it like it's Ren-chan!
The seniors are so confident!
Who the hell is Sugawara's true love?
Tamura!
IwamotoIwamoto, I had already warned you that I wouldn't forgive you if you didn't pick me in case something like this happened.
I've been telling him for a long time... but he didn't show up... but there's a reason.
Tamura got it, and it's kind of boring from Tamura's point of view.
No, no, no.
And Shibata, too.
I'll let you touch my cheeks.
I'll touch your cheeks.
Oh, no, this conversation's not good.
It's a proud thing to do.
I'm proud of you.
I'm getting into position.
It's not good to get into shape.
So Sugawara expressed his gratitude and confessed his love to Tamura, who had helped him a lot from praying for a hit when he first joined the group to having meals with him.
Please don't get on my bad side just because I didn't get it.
It's going to be a conversation now.
The next person to run for the job of taking care of Kawasaki was...
Oh, wait a minute, Yodare!
Five of us, including Endo, have already gotten one.
Let's start with Endo and ask him why.Okay, Endo... let's hear why.
He said he auditioned for Nogizaka because of you.
She said that.
That's what he said.
It's so strong!
It's confirmed! It's confirmed!
He changed my life.
Let's go.
Can we go on like this?
Mr. Tsutsui is standing proudly.
Here you go.
She said it's like an entrance ceremony.
It's nice, isn't it?
I'm filled with anticipation.
Good luck.
Ms. Sui.
Hey, it's me.
Yes, ma'am.
Why?
She told me she loved me.
We also went out to eat.
Dinner?
What did you go out to eat?
Yakiniku.
There it is.
All you eat is yakiniku?
I've eaten a lot of yakiniku.
So far... Tawamana went to a barbecue place too.
So it's pretty much a done deal.
It's close.It's close.
Why are you here?
Come to the radio once.
Yes, sir.
I don't like to smile with my teeth.
But you told me that you admired Kaki's model smile and that you were trying to emulate it.
Oh, that's what you said.
I wasn't aware of that, it just came out on its own.
(laughs)
I thought it would be great if I could smile like that.
That's a great episode.
I thought we got along really well.
You two get along? We talk a lot.
She's been drunk from the very beginning, calling me Ayame.
Ayame-sha!
Ayame-shaan?
And with Ayame, even when she doesn't speak, she says she doesn't mind.
Come on, Yumiki, are you okay?
To be honest, she calls me Yumiki, too.
Smile, really.
Kawasaki has a lisp, you know?
Like Yumiki Kyan.
The song "Hitori-sama Tengoku" has a lot of jumping.
"I'm tired of jumping.
So what?
Are you going to tell Yumiki that?
You don't tell your senpai that you're tired of the choreography.
That's right. You're either open-minded or a loser.
Either or.
Now, is there anyone Kawasaki wants to give a year-end gift to?Now, who is Kawasaki's true love?
Who is Kawasaki's true love?
No one?
It's on, it's on, it's on, it's on, it's on, it's on.
Dah!
Yoda!
I got my second Yoda!
Yay!
Yakiniku!
Yoda-da!
Tsutsui, how did it go?
I was pretty confident.
Really?
Why?
Tsutsui asked quickly, but for the first time, he sounded a little like this.
That's why I just heard the sound of his heart starting to crack.
Tsutsui just did that, didn't he?
And Kawasaki confessed his love.
Why did you choose Yoda?
I joined two years later than you.
I was really worried about it at the time.
And Yoda-san sent me a line so long that it couldn't fit in one scroll.
I don't have that image of Yoda.
Yoda was already limited to two lines.
Why is that?
But she did.
It was such a long message, and they hadn't even met yet.
Yes... I was really moved by that.
I see.
After that, on the day of shooting the 17-minute music video... After that, on the day of shooting the 17-minute music video
I was really looking forward to seeing Sakura-chan at the center early in the morning.
She has always supported me at every milestone, like sending me messages telling me to keep up the good work.
I see.
For supporting me.
Isn't that great?
Even when I asked for advice...
Like right now.
It's funny.
But he really was like that.
Ikeda then thanked his senpai
You can have it, senpai!
I'd like to have some of that.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Up, up, up!
Who were the three who ran for the position of "I, too, can get a birthday present from Ikeda"?
They were all in line for the thinnest episode of getting a birthday present.
Wait a minute, but I'm the kinkiest.
It's August 8th.
I'm closer.
We're the same.
Is there a senior here who had Ikeda's heart?
Go ahead.
Mold!
Cuelens!
Thank you. Thank you.
What's going on?What's wrong?
What's going on?
I don't really have any episodes with my seniors.
I was wondering if anyone could help me.
Is that what this is about?
Don't worry, I'm here.
Okay, I'm great.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna have to ask you both to leave.
Oh, hey, let me bet on it.
You've been a great help to me.
Time for Ikeda's tearful confession.
Why did you choose Paki?
Because I like him.
Because you like him?
What do you like about her?
She's so sparkly.
What? What? What?
I made a mistake.
Then who's the senior who ran for Nakanishi's year-end gift?
Go ahead.
One, two, three, two.
The three who came forward here... are the ones who keep getting rejected.
Frog boy's here again.
Hey, hey, hey! Amukaer!
Yes, well, I like reptiles.
You're pushing frogs again, aren't you?
I'm not a reptile myself, but I like frogs too.
We went out to play and eat together.
You do? Yes, I do. Are you doing it? Yes, ma'am.
What did you eat?
Hey, what did you eat?
Yakiniku.
Oh, it's confirmed.
It's confirmed.
Yakiniku reach!
Yakiniku... when I played with him... he said it was the first time he played with his seniors.
So it's the first time I've played with a senior.
So you already got the first one.
Yes, I did.
That's a big one.
Oh, Seimya!
Seimya's here.
You all know it.
You all know.
It was just a moment at the beginning of the actuary.
We did it together.
Also, at the Under Live, I was very aggressive and said, "Let's be friends.
I was very aggressive.
I don't really show it to my juniors, but...
But there was one thing that I was better than them.
I can go like this.
Wow.
So I'm happy if I can make them laugh.
Yes, now that's great!
But I think it's important for younger students to do the same.
I wonder if that's true.
I think so.I think so.
Oh, there it is again.
Hey...
Azu Chiba
Azu Chiba.
I'm from Chiba, too.
This is a big place.
No, it's a big place.
Chiba has a lot of 5th terms, right?
There's still so many.
Oh, you still have more?
We're the same age.
The same age?
We performed at the Coming-of-Age Ceremony together.
And we did a unit song together.
I see.
Yes, I see.
Then how are their relationships with each other?
I don't know.
That's what he said.
huh?
Is Nakanishi's true love among them?
Nakanishi chose...
It's moving.
Are they here or not?
Oh!
There it is!It's out!
It's gone!
Yakiniku!
Yakiniku is so strong!
Yakiniku.
Oh, no, it didn't work...
I have to go to Yakiniku.
Seimiya too... we have to go more often.
I have to invite him.
Wait a minute!
He's down on his knees.
2024.
And a confession of love from Nakanishi.
The reason I chose to go across the street...
It's really early days.
When I didn't know what was right and what was left
I was already having a hard time.
He took me to reptile cafes and stuff.
Heh.
That made me so happy.
I decided
I decided that if there was a project like this, I would definitely give it to him.
So that's what happened.
What's in this?
It's a catalog gift of meat!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Giving her a catalog gift is very thoughtful of you.I mean, it sounds really nice to give her a catalog gift, but...
But it means we can have a barbecue party at home.
Let's eat together!
Music video for new single "Monopoly" is now available!
Tickets to watch the live streaming of Shinyama Mono are now on sale!
Semi-array.
I've been working hard on growing out my hair lately.
It's almost like a bob now.
My goal is to grow it this long.
I'll do my best!
Please subscribe to my channel!
Bye bye!